- Why?
- So we can communicate through the wall.
(Leonard:)We are communicating through the wall.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but the communication
is not encrypted.
- I don't know Morse code.
- Oh, it's very simple. This is A.
[SHELDON KNOCKING ON WALL]
(Sheldon:)This is B.
- This is C.
- I'm not going to learn Morse code...
...at 3:00 in the morning.
(Penny:)All right.
(Leonard:)Don't come in here. Don't come in here.
Don't come in here. Don't...
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Leonard:)- What's going on?
- Shh. Ramona's sleeping on the couch.
- I know. When is she going home?
- Never. That's the problem.
(Sheldon:)- I need your help.
- What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)I'm invoking the Skynet clause
of our friendship agreement.
(Leonard:)That only applies
if you need me to help you destroy...
(Leonard:)...an artificial intelligence you created
that's taking over the earth.
Come on, don't nitpick.
- Good night.
- All right.